<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on TheDistroHopper</title><link>https://thedistrohopper.github.io/sarve.sh/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on TheDistroHopper</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>The content for this site is [CC-BY-SA](https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/deed.en)</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thedistrohopper.github.io/sarve.sh/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Stoic Principles for Software Engineers</title><link>https://thedistrohopper.github.io/sarve.sh/posts/stoic-principles-for-software-engineers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thedistrohopper.github.io/sarve.sh/posts/stoic-principles-for-software-engineers/</guid><description>I am a Software Engineer (SWE) by profession. The work of a SWE involves designing software, writing code, and solving problems. Software Engineering or any Engineering for that matter, tests the mental strength of an Engineer. This mental strength is the true power. Making clear decisions based on the clarity of information available is the real skill of a SWE. I constantly look to improve my thought process and cut the unwanted noise from my life.</description></item><item><title>Distro Hopping, A Rabbit Hole</title><link>https://thedistrohopper.github.io/sarve.sh/posts/distro-hopping/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thedistrohopper.github.io/sarve.sh/posts/distro-hopping/</guid><description>Distro hopping is a habit of computer users who chase the perfect setup of a distribution. A distribution is an operating system built from the Linux kernel and GNU utilities. Even after finding the ultimate distribution, the user doesn&amp;rsquo;t stop. They keep distro hopping and repeat the same loop over and over again without realizing the waste of time. Such users are called distro hoppers.
I was a distro hopper until I started working professionally in 2022.</description></item><item><title>Welcome..!</title><link>https://thedistrohopper.github.io/sarve.sh/posts/welcome/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://thedistrohopper.github.io/sarve.sh/posts/welcome/</guid><description>Hello there, I am Sarvesh, a computer science graduate working as a backend developer.
This blog will be used to share my learnings, perspectives and opinions.
I like to keep things simple and minimal. So that&amp;rsquo;s it for the first post.</description></item></channel></rss>